All men are created evil.
Nature of the Beast is a crime, thriller, mystery film directed by Victor Salva.
Two men, both hiding a deadly secret, are on a
murderous rampage through the desert.
Jack Powell, played by Lance Henriksen.
Adrian, played by Eric Roberts.
Sheriff Gordon, played by Brion James.
Manfred, played by Frank Novak.
Gerald, played by Sasha Jenson.
Dahlia, played by Ana Gabriel.
Nature of the Beast (European title: Bad Company, UK title: Hatchet Man) is a 1995 American direct-to-video
mystery horror film written and directed by Victor Salva and starring Eric Roberts and Lance Henriksen.
The film explores themes of motel, highway, diner, murder, serial killer.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.